A Guide to the Graham T. T. Molitor Papers FA074
Rockefeller Archive Center
Graham T. T. Molitor papers
1953-1968
Rockefeller Archive Center
Molitor, Graham T. T. (Graham Thomas Tate)
FA074
36 Cubic Feet 36 document cases
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical/Historical note
Graham Molitor was born in Seattle in 1934. He earned a B.A. degree from the University of Washington in 1955 and an LL.B. degree from the American University in 1963. He was admitted to the bar in the District of Columbia in 1963. After working as a court bailiff in the District of Columbia and as a legislative counsel in the House of Representatives, Mr. Molitor was hired as Director of Candidate Research of the Rockefeller for President Committee in 1963. He was responsible for monitoring and analyzing statements made by other candidates for the Republican presidential nomination. He served until Governor Rockefeller withdrew his candidacy in 1964, and then served in the same capacity again in Governor Rockefeller's 1968 presidential campaign. From 1963 to 1977 he worked as a lobbyist for the food industry. In 1977 he established Public Policy Forecasting, Inc., and has written, lectured, consulted and participated in numerous public policy conferences all regarding future trends in food, technology and related public policy issues.
Scope and Contents note
Records of the director of opposition research during Rockefeller's 1964 and 1968 presidential campaigns. Documents, statements, and policy positions of Barry Goldwater, Richard Nixon, and other prospective opponents.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV 3A 18
Arrangement
As received.
Presidents -- United States -- Election-1968; Political science; Political campaigns -- United States; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; United States; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Molitor, Graham T. T. (Graham Thomas Tate); Kennedy, Robert F.; McCarthy, Eugene J.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous); Reagan, Ronald; Scranton, William Warren; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich); Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio); Goldwater, Barry M. (Barry Morris)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - BMG - ADA Blast (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Agriculture (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Alliances (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Appalachia (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Appropriation (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Arms Control (Agency) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Business, Commerce and Banking (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Captive Nations (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Central Arizona Project (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Centralized Government (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Church-State (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Civil Defense (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Civil Defense - Civil Rights, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Civil Defense - Civil Rights, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Transcript Clippings (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Civil Service (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Communications (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Communism - International, Cold War, Communist Threat (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Communism - Subversive Activities (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Communism - General (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Department Store Solution (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Depressed Areas (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Desalinization (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Disarmament (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - District of Columbia (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Domestic Service Corps (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Economy - Impact of BMG's Election on the Economy (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Economy - National Debt (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Education - BMG Study, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Education - BMG Study, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Education - BMG Study, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Aid (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Aid - Peace Corps (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Aid - General (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Africa (Colonialism) (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Berlin (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Berlin Wall (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Communist China (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Congo (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Cuba, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Cuba, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Cuban Water Shut Off (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Cyprus (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Eastern Europe (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - France (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Germany (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Greek Elections (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - India (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Laos (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Latin America (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Middle East (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Panama (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Puerto Rico (Statehood) (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Rash Statements (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Southeast Asia (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Soviet Union - Wheat Deal (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Soviet Union - Withdrawing Diplomatic Recognition (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Soviet Union - General (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Vietnam (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Vietnam - General, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Vietnam - General, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Foreign Trade (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Government Organization (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Health (Medical Care) (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Highway (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Housing and Urban Affairs (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Immigration (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Indian Affairs (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Individualism (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Judiciary - Supreme Court (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Judiciary - General (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Labor, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Labor, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Liberalism (Socialism) (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Library Services Act (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Medicare (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Military (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Minimum Wage Duplicates (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Minimum Wage Laws (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Mining (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Missiles - One in Moscow Men's Room (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Missiles - Missile Reliability, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Missiles - Missile Reliability, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Natural Resources (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Negotiations (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Nepotism (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - News Management (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Nuclear Defoliation of Southeast Asia (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Nuclear Testing - Plowshare Project (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Nuclear Testing - Test Ban Treaty Renunciation, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Nuclear Testing - Test Ban Treaty Renunciation, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Nuclear Testing - Willingness to Use Nuclear Weapons, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Nuclear Testing - General (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Political Philosophy (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Post Office Department (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Poverty (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Public Power - TVA Sale Proposal, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Public Power - TVA Sale Proposal, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Public Power - TVA Pamphlets, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Public Power - TVA Pamphlets, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Public Power - General, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 104)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Public Power - General, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Public Works (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Regulatory Agencies (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Right-to-Work (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Rule XXII (Box 3, Folder 109)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Rules Committee Packing (Box 3, Folder 110)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - School Prayer Ban Decision (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Science and Government (Box 3, Folder 112)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Secrecy in Government (Box 3, Folder 113)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Social Security - Make Voluntary (Box 3, Folder 114)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Social Security - General (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Space Program (Box 3, Folder 116)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - State-Federal Relationship (Box 3, Folder 117)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Straight Ticket Voting (Box 3, Folder 118)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Taxation - Abolish Progressive Rate (Box 4, Folder 119)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Taxation - General (Box 4, Folder 120)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Transportation (Box 4, Folder 121)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - U2 Overflights (Box 4, Folder 122)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Unemployment (Box 4, Folder 123)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - United Nations - Charter Revision (Box 4, Folder 124)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - United Nations - Pulling Out (Box 4, Folder 125)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - United Nations - General, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 126)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - United Nations - General, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 127)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Urban Affairs (Box 4, Folder 128)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Utilities Regulations (Box 4, Folder 129)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Veterans (Box 4, Folder 130)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Water Pollution (Box 4, Folder 131)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Welfare (Box 4, Folder 132)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - World Court (Box 4, Folder 133)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Youth (Box 4, Folder 134)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - Youth Conservation Corps (Box 4, Folder 135)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Best Issues (Box 4, Folder 136)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Binder Tabs (Box 4, Folder 137)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Damaging Issues, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 138)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Damaging Issues, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 139)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Damaging Issues, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 140)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Damaging Issues, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 141)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Issue/Positions Summarization, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 142)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Issue/Positions Summarization, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 143)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Issue/Positions Summarization, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 144)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Positions on Issues - General - Miscellaneous Files (Box 4, Folder 145)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Candidacy Announcement (Box 5, Folder 146)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Conservative Groups Campaign Material for BMG, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 147)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Conservative Groups Campaign Material for BMG, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 148)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Contributions (Box 5, Folder 149)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - 1960 GOP Convention (Box 5, Folder 150)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - 1968 GOP Convention (Box 5, Folder 151)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - CRA Answers (Box 5, Folder 152)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Delegate Support, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 153)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Delegate Support, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 154)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Democratic Party (Box 5, Folder 155)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Candidate Draft Position (Box 5, Folder 156)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Dual Candidacy (Box 5, Folder 157)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Family Participation (Box 5, Folder 158)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Freedom Special (BMG's Campaign Newsletter) (Box 5, Folder 159)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - GOP - Attacks on BMG (Box 5, Folder 160)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Election Analysis and Notes (Box 5, Folder 161)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - 1968 GOP Platform (Box 5, Folder 162)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - GOP - Newsletter (Box 5, Folder 163)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - BMG Heading Ticket Injuries GOP Prospects (Box 5, Folder 164)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Itinerary (Box 5, Folder 165)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Magazines (Box 5, Folder 166)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - BMG's Campaign News Releases (Box 5, Folder 167)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Nominations (Box 5, Folder 168)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Divisive Influences and Party Unity Platforms (Box 5, Folder 169)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - 1960 GOP Platforms (Box 5, Folder 170)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - 1964 GOP Platforms (Box 5, Folder 171)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - Analysis Notebook, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 172)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - Analysis Notebook, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 173)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - Analysis Notebook, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 174)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - Analysis Notebook, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 175)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - Platform Comparison (Box 5, Folder 176)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Platforms - "The Looser the Better" (Box 5, Folder 177)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Polls (Box 5, Folder 178)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Primaries - Interpretations (Box 5, Folder 179)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Primaries - Results (Box 5, Folder 180)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Questions to Candidates (Box 5, Folder 181)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Republican Party - Repudiation of the Party Platform (Box 5, Folder 182)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Republican Party - Declaration of Republican Principle and Policy (Box 5, Folder 183)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Republican Party - General (Box 5, Folder 184)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - "The South" (Box 5, Folder 185)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - California - Comments if BMG had lost the California Primary (Box 5, Folder 186)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - California - General (Box 5A, Folder 187)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - New Hampshire, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 5A, Folder 188)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - New Hampshire, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 5A, Folder 189)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - Oregon (Box 5A, Folder 190)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - Other States (Box 5A, Folder 191)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - California - General (Box 5A, Folder 187)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - New Hampshire, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 5A, Folder 188)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - New Hampshire, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 5A, Folder 189)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - Oregon (Box 5A, Folder 190)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - States - Other States (Box 5A, Folder 191)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Strategy (Box 6, Folder 192)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Voting Participation (Box 6, Folder 193)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Literature, Folder 1 of 6 (Box 6, Folder 194)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Literature, Folder 2 of 6 (Box 6, Folder 195)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Literature, Folder 3 of 6 (Box 6, Folder 196)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Literature, Folder 4 of 6 (Box 6, Folder 197)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Literature, Folder 5 of 6 (Box 6, Folder 198)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Campaign Literature, Folder 6 of 6 (Box 6, Folder 199)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - General - Political Profiles of the State (Box 6, Folder 200)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - General - Miscellaneous Campaign Material (Box 6, Folder 201)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 6, Folder 202)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Civil Defense (Box 6, Folder 203)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Civil Service (Box 6, Folder 204)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Communication Satellite Act (Box 6, Folder 205)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Defense (Box 6, Folder 206)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Disarmament (Box 6, Folder 207)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Education, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 208)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Education, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 209)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Aid (Box 6, Folder 210)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Alliance System (Box 6, Folder 211)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Africa (Box 6, Folder 212)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Berlin (Box 6, Folder 213)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Communism (Box 6, Folder 214)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Communist China (Box 6, Folder 215)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Cuba (Box 6, Folder 216)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Eastern Europe (Box 6, Folder 217)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Germany (Box 6, Folder 218)